const nflTriviData = [
  {
    category: "Teams",
    question:
      "Who was picked first overall by the St. Louis Rams in the 2010 NFL Draft?",
    A: "Sam Bradford",
    B: "Mat Stafford",
    C: "Jimmy Garoppolo",
    ans: "A: Sam Bradford",
  },
  {
    category: "Teams",
    question: "Which was the first team to win the NFL Super Bowl?",
    A: "Chiefs",
    B: "Green Bay",
    C: "Giants",
    ans: "B: Green Bay",
  },
  {
    category: "Teams",
    question: "The NFL team based in Kansas City has which nickname?",
    A: "Commanders",
    B: "Chiefs",
    C: "Jaguars",
    ans: "B: Chiefs",
  },
  {
    category: "Teams",
    question: "In which city are the NFL side the 'Bengals' based?",
    A: "Indianapolis",
    B: "Phoenix",
    C: "Cincinnati",
    ans: "C: Cincinatti",
  },
  {
    category: "Teams",
    question: "The Chargers are the NFL team based in which city?",
    A: "San Diego",
    B: "Los Angels",
    C: "Denver",
    ans: "A: San Diego",
  },
  {
    category: "Teams",
    question: "In which city are the NFL Ravens based?",
    A: "Foxboro",
    B: "New York",
    C: "Baltimore",
    ans: "C: Baltimore",
  },
  {
    category: "Teams",
    question: "The NFL Team known as the Bears are located in which US City?",
    A: "Chicago",
    B: "Pittsburgh",
    C: "Boston",
    ans: "A: Chicago",
  },
  {
    category: "Teams",
    question: "Which team has won the most Super Bowls?",
    A: "Green Bay Packers",
    B: "Patriots",
    C: "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    ans: "C: Pittsburgh Steelers",
  },
  {
    category: "Teams",
    question: "The Browns are the NFL team in which city?",
    A: "Cleveland",
    B: "Cincinati",
    C: "Denver",
    ans: "A: Cleveland",
  },
  {
    category: "Teams",
    question:
      "Which team allowed the most passing yards in the 2013 NFL season?",
    A: "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    B: "Patriots",
    C: "Philadelphia Eagles",
    ans: "C: Philadelphia Eagles",
  },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "In which city are the 'Texans' based?",
  //   A: "Dallas",
  //   B: "Houston",
  //   C: "Ft. Worth",
  //   ans: "B: Houston",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "What city are the Cowboys from?",
  //   A: "Dallas",
  //   B: "Houston",
  //   C: "Ft. Worth",
  //   ans: "A: Dallas",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "In which state are the 'Cardinals' based?",
  //   A: "Arizona",
  //   B: "Scottsdale",
  //   C: "Phoenix",
  //   ans: "C: Phoenix",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "In which city are the 'Broncos' based?",
  //   A: "Denver",
  //   B: "Boulder",
  //   C: "Aspen",
  //   ans: "A: Denver",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "Which team scored the most points in the 2013 NFL season?",
  //   A: "Chargers",
  //   B: "Broncos",
  //   C: "Eagles",
  //   ans: "B: Broncos",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "In which city do the Bills play?",
  //   A: "Buffalo",
  //   B: "New York",
  //   C: "Boston",
  //   ans: "A: Buffalo",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "The Dolphins can be found as the NFL team of which city?",
  //   A: "Tampa Bay",
  //   B: "Jacksonville",
  //   C: "Miami",
  //   ans: "C: Miami",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "In which city are the 'Panthers' based?",
  //   A: "Carolina",
  //   B: "Charlotte",
  //   C: "Raleigh",
  //   ans: "B: Charlotte",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "In which city do the Patriots play?",
  //   A: "Boston",
  //   B: "Providence",
  //   C: "Foxboro",
  //   ans: "C: Foxboro",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question:
  //     "Which is the only NFL team that plays their home games in New York state?",
  //   A: "Buffalo Bills",
  //   B: "Giants",
  //   C: "Jets",
  //   ans: "A: Buffalo Bills",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "In which city do the Giants allege they are based?",
  //   A: "New York",
  //   B: "Newark",
  //   C: "Delaware",
  //   ans: "A: New York",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "In which city are the Raiders based?",
  //   A: "Los Angels",
  //   B: "Oakland",
  //   C: "Las Vegas",
  //   ans: "C: Las Vegas",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "In which city are the the Seahawks based?",
  //   A: "Seattle",
  //   B: "Spokane",
  //   C: "Olympia",
  //   ans: "A: Seattle",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "The Packers compete in the NFL representing which city?",
  //   A: "Madison",
  //   B: "Green Bay",
  //   C: "Indianapolis",
  //   ans: "B: Green Bay",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "In which city are the NFL side the '49ers' based?",
  //   A: "San Francisco",
  //   B: "Los Angels",
  //   C: "Oakland",
  //   ans: "A: San Francisco",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "In which city are the NFL side the 'Buccaneers' based?",
  //   A: "Miami",
  //   B: "Nashville",
  //   C: "Tampa Bay",
  //   ans: "C: Tampa Bay",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Teams",
  //   question: "In which city are the NFL side the 'Redskins' based?",
  //   A: "Washington",
  //   B: "Boston",
  //   C: "Minneapolis",
  //   ans: "A: Washington",
  // },
  {
    category: "Players & Coaches",
    question:
      "Which NFL referee is known for wearing tight shirts and flexing for the cameras while making on-field calls?",
    A: "Ed Hochuli",
    B: "Brett Favre",
    C: "Antonio Brown",
    ans: "A: Ed Hochuli",
  },
  {
    category: "Players & Coaches",
    question:
      "Who won his third National Football League Coach of the Year Award in 2010?",
    A: "Anquan Boldin",
    B: "Bill Belichick",
    C: "Carson Wentz",
    ans: "B: Bill Belichick",
  },
  {
    category: "Players & Coaches",
    question:
      "Which NFL player joined the Kansas City Chiefs from the San Francisco 49ers in February 2013?",
    A: "Jim Thorpe",
    B: "Drew Bledsoe",
    C: "Alex Smith",
    ans: "C: Alex Smith",
  },
  {
    category: "Players & Coaches",
    question:
      "Which NFL quarterback is known by the nickname 'The Gunslinger'?",
    A: "Brett Favre",
    B: "Russel Wilson",
    C: "Le'Veon Bell",
    ans: "A: Brett Favre",
  },
  {
    category: "Players & Coaches",
    question: "Who won PFWA NFL Executive of the Year for the 2013 NFL season?",
    A: "John Dorsey",
    B: "Aaron Rodgers",
    C: "Todd Gurley",
    ans: "A: John Dorsey",
  },
  {
    category: "Players & Coaches",
    question: "Who won the 2012 NFL MVP Award?",
    A: "Greg Jennings",
    B: "Rob Gronkowski",
    C: "Adrian Peterson",
    ans: "C: Adria Peterson",
  },
  {
    category: "Players & Coaches",
    question:
      "In NFL which wide receiver made 101 catches in his Arizona Cardinals rookie season?",
    A: "Eric Fisher",
    B: "Anquan Boldin",
    C: "Von Miller",
    ans: "B: Anquan Boldin",
  },
  {
    category: "Players & Coaches",
    question: "Which famous NFL player is Native American?",
    A: "Russell Wilson",
    B: "Jim Thorpe",
    C: "Luke Kuechly",
    ans: "B: Jim Thorpe",
  },
  {
    category: "Players & Coaches",
    question: "Who was selected first in the 2012 NFL Draft?",
    A: "David Carr",
    B: "Joe Buck",
    C: "Andrew Luck",
    ans: "C: Andrew Luck",
  },
  {
    category: "Players & Coaches",
    question:
      "Which NFL player joined the Minnesota Vikings from the Green Bay Packers in 2013?",
    A: "Lenny Moore",
    B: "Greg Jennings",
    C: "Rob Riggle",
    ans: "A: Lenny Moore",
  },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question:
  //     "In NFL which Houston Oilers player was nicknamed 'The Human Bowling Ball'?",
  //   A: "Percy Harvin",
  //   B: "Charlie Tolar",
  //   C: "Jalen Ramsey",
  //   ans: "A: Percy Harvin",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question:
  //     "Which NFL player joined the San Francisco 49ers from the Baltimore Ravens in March 2013?",
  //   A: "Michael Vick",
  //   B: "Anquan Boldin",
  //   C: "Ben Roethlisberger",
  //   ans: "C: Ben Roethlisberger",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question:
  //     "Which NFL player joined the Denver Broncos from the New England Patriots in 2013?",
  //   A: "Percy Harvin",
  //   B: "Wes Welker",
  //   C: "Bobby Wagner",
  //   ans: "B: Wes Welker",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question:
  //     "Which NFL player joined the Tampa Bay Buccaneers from the San Francisco 49ers in 2013?",
  //   A: "Dashon Goldson",
  //   B: "Travis Kelce",
  //   C: "Cameron Jordan",
  //   ans: "A: Dashon Goldson",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question: "Who was selected first in the 2013 NFL Draft?",
  //   A: "Philip Rivers",
  //   B: "Eric Fisher",
  //   C: "Cam Newton",
  //   ans: "B: Eric Fisher",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question:
  //     "Which NFL player joined the Miami Dolphins from the Pittsburgh Steelers in 2013?",
  //   A: "Mike Wallace",
  //   B: "Aaron Donald",
  //   C: "Larry Fitzgerald",
  //   ans: "A: Mike Wallace",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question: "Who won the 2012 AP NFL Coach of the Year Award?",
  //   A: "Peyton Manning",
  //   B: "Bruce Arians",
  //   C: "Chandlre Jones",
  //   ans: "B: Bruce Arians",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question:
  //     "In the 2013 season which player led the NFL in terms of total licensed product sales?",
  //   A: "Marcus Welby",
  //   B: "Christian MCCaffrey",
  //   C: "Russell Wilson",
  //   ans: "C: Russel Wilson",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question:
  //     "Which NFL player joined the Detroit Lions from the Miami Dolphins in 2013?",
  //   A: "Reggie Bush",
  //   B: "George Kittle",
  //   C: "Matt Ryan",
  //   ans: "A: Reggie Bush",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question: "Who was selected first in the 2002 NFL Draft?",
  //   A: "Kurt Warner",
  //   B: "David Carr",
  //   C: "LeSean McCoy",
  //   ans: "B: David Carr",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question:
  //     "In the 1960s who scored a record touchdown in 18 consecutive NFL games?",
  //   A: "Tom Brady",
  //   B: "Lenny Moore",
  //   C: "Matt Stafford",
  //   ans: "B: Lenny Moore",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question:
  //     "Which NFL player joined the Seattle Seahawks from the Minnesota Vikings in March 2013?",
  //   A: "Patrick Mahomes",
  //   B: "Percy Harvin",
  //   C: "Matt Ryan",
  //   ans: "C: Matt Ryan",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question: "Who was selected first in the 2001 NFL Draft?",
  //   A: "Tom Landry",
  //   B: "Michael Vick",
  //   C: "Jadeveon Clowney",
  //   ans: "C: Jadeveen Clowney",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question:
  //     "Which NFL player joined the Indianapolis Colts from the Cleveland Browns in September 2013?",
  //   A: "Josh Allen",
  //   B: "Trent Richardson",
  //   C: "Kareem Hunt",
  //   ans: "C: Kareem Hunt",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question:
  //     "Which NFL player joined the Miami Dolphins from the New England Patriots in 2013?",
  //   A: "Wes Welker",
  //   B: "DeAndre Hopkins",
  //   C: "Jared Goff",
  //   ans: "A: Wes Welker",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question: "Which team had the first pick in the 2013 NFL Draft?",
  //   A: "Miami Dolphins",
  //   B: "Kansas City Chiefs",
  //   C: "Denver Broncos",
  //   ans: "B: Kansas City Chiefs",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question:
  //     "Which NFL player joined the Tampa Bay Buccaneers from the New York Jets in April 2013?",
  //   A: "Darrelle Revis",
  //   B: "Stephon Gilmore",
  //   C: "Tyron Smith",
  //   ans: "A: Darrelle Revis",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question: "Who won AP Comeback Player of the Year for the 2013 NFL season?",
  //   A: "Tyreek Hill",
  //   B: "Julio Jones",
  //   C: "Philip Rivers",
  //   ans: "C: Philip Rivers",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question: "Who was selected first in the 2007 NFL Draft?",
  //   A: "Joe Burrow",
  //   B: "Bobby Wagner",
  //   C: "JaMarcus Russell",
  //   ans: "C: JaMarcus Russell",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question: "Who was selected first in the 2004 NFL Draft?",
  //   A: "Nick Bosa",
  //   B: "Drew Brees",
  //   C: "Eli Manning",
  //   ans: "C: Eli Manning",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question: "Who was selected first in the 1997 NFL Draft?",
  //   A: "Jalen Hurts",
  //   B: "Orlando Pace",
  //   C: "Earl Thomas",
  //   ans: "B: Orlando Price",
  // },
  // {
  //   category: "Players & Coaches",
  //   question: "Who was named MVP for the 2013 NFL season?",
  //   A: "Justin Jefferson",
  //   B: "Peyton Manning",
  //   C: "Davante Adams",
  //   ans: "B: Peyton Manning",
  // },
];
export default nflTriviData;
